{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/4977","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4977","name":"Jungle Juice","address":"4000 St. Jean","zipcode":"48214","owner":"","licenseNumber":"082490","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Permanently Closed","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"335","coords":"","geojson":{"id":"4977","type":"Feature","geometry":null,"properties":{"name":"Jungle Juice","owner":"","address":"4000 St. Jean","zipcode":"48214","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"082490","establishmentid":"4977","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Permanently Closed","review_frequency_days":"335","most_recent_license_date":"2018-04-30"}},"nearbyList":[],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43951","inspectionDate":"2018-10-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"At the Bleach","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-11-26T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"Missing Paper toweling","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-10-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"At the Lights","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Stove","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"40461","inspectionDate":"2017-10-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Ice machine","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Ice machine","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at 30 inches above the floor","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at 30 inches above the floor","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"At the Lights","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the PERSON IN CHARGE","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"Missing Covered waste container","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"}]},{"inspectionid":"36377","inspectionDate":"2016-09-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"At the Lights","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4977"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}